And then finally, use your coach. This is the flowing process. So
flowing is a daily process that you can come in and actually
talk to an AI or use it in a text version based
upon the triggers that you have.
One big thing you must do first is set up your AI
profile, right? So you can edit it manually or you can do
a really cool thing which is basically talk to an AI bot
that's going to help you deepen your profile by asking very specific
questions for you.
So you want to make sure that is, that is what's going
on. As we come down here, the way that you flow is
simply by clicking what you'd like.
If I click on discovery flow, it's going to bring me into
a new thing. I'm going to delete the old one.
It's gonna say, Do you want to do test? Or voice? If
I want to do voice, I could just do an AI voice
and talk to it, but I'm going to choose text for now.
And this is what it looks like. It's basically saying, take a
breath, give a discovery a short title. I can say, my training
this week.
If I go past this, which core 4 is this in? I'm
going to say business. What was the source? Where did the learning
come from?
And I'm going to expand on that. So I'm going to use,
And a whisper flow from EMC. I did some one-on-one training with
a coach, and we had a great meeting, and I have my
plan for the next month mapped out, and I feel certain about
that.
Now I send that through, and now it's going to look at
this and basically say, alright, this is what he's doing.
Now we're going to start to expand a little bit to make
sure that we can, have a conversation about what this means for
him and what's going on.
Now the coach is thinking because we want to make sure the
AI is seeing what's going on and also looking at my past
history to make sure it's applying what's going on.
So, what part of the meeting changed what you actually want will
do when the resistance shows up. Not just how certain you feel
right now.
So it's slowly trying to integrate me into action. Okay. I'm not
going to continue in this, but as you can see, it's a
conversation that can happen and it tracks you from a point perspective.
So you get seven total points for flows a week. You can
do 15 flows in a week, but we're only going to give
you seven points to make sure you do and keep your discipline
every single day.
And as you can see, when you miss it, you miss it.
You can't go back and actually do it again.